A biblical assault on the senses!
Fist of Jesus is a comedy, action, horror film directed by David Muñoz.
When Jacob tells Jesus that Lazarus, his son, is dead, he
goes to his house to raise him from the dead.
Jesus, played by Marc Velasco.
Judas, played by Noé Blancafort.
Jacob, played by Salvador Llós.
Sara, played by Victoria Roldán.
Lazarus, played by Roger Sotera.
Cowboy Boss, played by José María Angorrilla.
Fist of Jesus is a 2012 Spanish splatter comedy short film
about Jesus Christ in a zombie apocalypse.
The film explores themes of gore, jesus freak, zombie
apocalypse, jesus christ, short film.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.